j_mansito@yahoo.com • <u>linkedin</u> 210-882-0960 • Golden, Colorado

Business Professional Profile

Qualifications Summary

Detail oriented and experienced professional with progressive experience managing teams and projects to promote organizational objectives. Accomplished salesman with 10+ years in sales, project management, and team management. Talented communicator, able to effectively resolve conflict, train and mentor staff, and manage complex relationships. Analyze information and implement system and process improvements to increase efficiency.

- Customer Service
- Schedule Management
- Staff Training & Leadership
- Conflict Resolution
- Research & Analysis
- Relationship Management
- Salesmanship
- MS Office
- Communication

Career Experience

Assistant Manager II, Men's Wearhouse, Lakewood, Colorado

2018 to Present

Manage a \$3.5M, 5K square foot location of a national men's clothing chain. Provide oversight and excellent leadership and guidance to staff members. Monitor and maintain store inventory, review merchandising, analyze product trends, and implement promotions to improve sales. Recruit, hire, train, mentor, and inspire employees to promote professional development and maintain excellent customer service. Lead the team in all sales categories and provide a world class experience to all guests in the store.

- Currently top 10 in the company for multiple sales categories.
- Developed a new sales strategy that increased custom suit sales by 30%.

Store Manager, Mattress Firm, Denver, Colorado

2017 to 2018

Delivered operational excellence and executed strategic processes to achieve sales goals within home store environment. Managed and maintained store inventory and ensured store appearance and merchandising reflected company standards and encouraged sales. Communicated and implemented policy and procedure changes to increase traffic and revenue. Recruited, trained, and mentored staff to improve product knowledge and promote sales. Set staff schedule and oversaw all internal projects.

- Recognized with multiple top salesman awards for exceeding sales targets and delivering exceptional customer service experiences.
- Increased store profits by 50% in my first year and became one of the top stores in Denver.

Business and Project Manager, S&J Enterprise, San Antonio, Texas

2011 to 2018

Led daily operations for a company offering small- and large-scale remodeling and new build services for residential homes. Promoted services and performed business development tasks to retain clients, established project budgets and schedules, and assembled project teams to complete projects within time and budget restrictions. Administered payroll, processed business expenses, and completed all

Josh Mansito

accounts tasks. Trained and lead all daily tasks while ensuring world class customer satisfaction. Partnered with realtors to purchase and sell both residential and commercial properties, acting as the lead salesman in deals.

System Designer, Magnolia Audio Video, Lakewood, Colorado

2016 to 2017

Coordinated schedules for projects, deliveries, client meetings, repairs, and travel to ensure accurate and efficient completion of work that met client expectations. Sold products, trained and coached staff, completed marketing and business development tasks, and followed-up with clients after installation to confirm everything was functioning properly.

• Delivered over \$1M in sales through the development of profitable relationships with high profile partners, resulting in major new projects.

Head Mixing Engineer, FireWave Productions, San Antonio, Texas

2013 to 2015

Led the recording process for music projects at a top three recording studio. Recorded, edited, mixed, and delivered projects for multiple clients each day, adhering to tight deadlines. Trained employees, and completed administrative tasks, including scheduling meetings, managing studio calendar, and providing exceptional service to clients while leading the mixing team.

Education

Business Management and Marketing Courses, University of Texas and Texas State University